In this exercise, we will be working the hamstrings very heavily.
What we are going to do, is begin by putting the ball under our legs and laying flat on our back.
So, support the abs.
Close the ribcage.
Curl down to come flat on your back and bring the ball under your legs.
From here, extend the ball out to ninety degrees.
Now, you want your feet kind of on the side of the ball.
We are going to go ahead and bridge up in one move.
Rather than articulate the spine.
So, take a nice inhale.
Exhale.
Close the ribcage and come up.
Inhale.
Hold.
Exhale.
Push the ball out.
Inhale.
Bring it in and come down.
Exhale.
Up.
Inhale.
Hold.
Exhale.
Out.
Inhale.
In.
And, exhale down.
Now, this exercise can be advanced by doing it with just one leg.